<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "https://resources.jetbrains.com/stardust/html-entities.dtd">

<topic xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://resources.jetbrains.com/stardust/topic.v2.xsd"
       xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
       title="Dragon Age: Inquisiotion XML"
       id="Dragon_Age__Inquisiotion_XML">
    <include src="ReuseMe.xml" include-id="reuse_DA_img"/>
    <microformat>
        <p>
            <emphasis>Dragon Age: Inquisition</emphasis>
            is <keyword>BioWare</keyword>'s third installment in the <emphasis>Dragon Age</emphasis> video game series,
            continuing the journey
            throughout the medieval-themed continent of Thedas introduced in Dragon Age: Origins and Dragon Age II.
            <video product="cv2" src="Rec0.mp4" preview-src="img_video_completion.png" origin="completion_on_video_module"/>
            <img product="cv2" src="img_video_completion.png" origin="completion_on_video_module"/>
        </p>
    </microformat>

<!--    <tip-of-the-day>-->
<!--        <p>-->
<!--            Tip-->
<!--        </p>-->
<!--    </tip-of-the-day>-->
    <chapter title="Characters" id="characters">
        <img src="Inquisition_members.png" alt="members" width="500"/>
        <tabs>
            <tab title="Major Characters">
                <list>
                    <li>The Inquisitor: The protagonist of the game and leader of the Inquisition.
                        <img src="inquisitor.jpg" alt="inquisitior" width="300" border-effect="shadow"/>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Cullen Rutherford: Advisor to the Inquisitor and a Knight-Captain of the Templar Order, who
                        witnessed the deeds of both the Hero of Ferelden and the Champion of Kirkwall. He leads the
                        Inquisition's military forces.
                        <img src="cullen.png" alt="Cullen" animated="true" width="300"></img>
                    </li>
                    <li>Elder One: A mysterious entity who is served by the Venatori and the Red Templars.
                        <img src="corypheus.png" alt="Elder One" animated="true" width="300"></img>
                    </li>
                    <li>Josephine Montilyet: Advisor to the Inquisitor, a skilled diplomat and an old friend of
                        Leliana.
                        <icon src="resources.idea-eap.png" alt="Resources Idea Eap"></icon>
                        <icon src="not-existing.png" alt="Not existing icon" nullable="true"></icon>
                    </li>
                    <li>Leliana: Advisor to the Inquisitor, the Left Hand of the Divine and, depending on player choice,
                        former companion of the Hero of Ferelden. She leads the clandestine division of the Inquisition
                        responsible for espionage and assassination.
                        <video src="ReSharper.mp4" preview-src="ReSharperJPG.jpg"></video>
                        <video src="ReSharper.mp4"></video>
                        <video src="ReSharper.mp4"></video>
                    </li>
                    <li>Morrigan: A Witch of the Wilds, a shapeshifting apostate mage, and former companion of the Hero
                        of Ferelden. She disappeared at the end of the Fifth Blight and reappeared years later as the
                        arcane advisor to Empress Celene.
                        <video href="qQovAuIz7wg"></video>
                    </li>
                </list>
            </tab>
            <tab title="Companions">
                <procedure style="steps" title="Characters" hide-from-structure="true">
                    <step>
                        <shortcut key="$Copy"></shortcut>
                        <shortcut>Ctrl + B, W</shortcut>
                        Blackwall: A Grey Warden of Orlais.
                    </step>
                    <step>Cassandra Pentaghast: The Right Hand of the Divine and one of the last loyal members of the
                        Seekers of Truth.
                    </step>
                    <step>Cole: A mysterious ghost-like rogue, first introduced in Dragon Age: Asunder.</step>
                    <step>Dorian Pavus: An Altus mage from the Tevinter Imperium.</step>
                    <step>Iron Bull: A Qunari mercenary and agent of the Ben-Hassrath.</step>
                    <step>Sera: An elven archer and member of the enigmatic group of rogues known as the Friends of Red
                        Jenny.
                    </step>
                    <step>Solas: An apostate elven mage and expert on the Fade.</step>
                    <step>Varric Tethras: A dwarven rogue and member of the Merchant's Guild. He is a consummate
                        storyteller and former companion of the Champion of Kirkwall.
                    </step>
                    <step>Vivienne: A Loyalist Circle mage and First Enchanter of Montsimmard as well as Enchantress to
                        the Imperial Court of Orlais.
                    </step>
                </procedure>
            </tab>
            <tab title="Secondary Characters">
                <table>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Name: Description</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Alexius: A member of the Magisterium who leads a band of Venatori into Redcliffe.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Alistair (conditional): A Grey Warden, former companion of the Hero of Ferelden and,
                            depending on player choice, King of Ferelden.
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Anora (conditional): Queen of Ferelden, depending on player choice.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Briala: Ambassador for the elves of Orlais.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Calpernia (conditional): Leader of the Venatori on behalf of the Elder One.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Celene Valmont I: Empress of Orlais.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Clarel: Warden-Commander of Orlais.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Dagna: A smith caste dwarf or scholar of the Circle of Magi, depending on player choice.
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Fiona: Former Grand Enchanter of the Circle of Magi, now leader of the mage rebellion. She
                            is also Alistair's mother and a former Grey Warden.
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Flemeth: The legendary Asha'bellanar, Witch of the Wilds, and mother of Morrigan.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Gaspard de Chalons: Grand Duke of Orlais, rival of Celene in the Orlesian Civil War.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Lace Harding: The dwarven head scout and lieutenant of the Inquisition.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Hawke: The protagonist of Dragon Age II, Champion of Kirkwall and, depending on player
                            choice, Viscount of Kirkwall.
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Justinia V: Divine of the Andrastian Chantry.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Loghain Mac Tir (conditional): Former Teyrn of Gwaren, father of Anora and, depending on
                            player choice, companion to the Hero of Fereldan.
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Mother Giselle: A Chantry Mother and early supporter of the Inquisition.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Samson (conditional): Leader of the Red Templars on behalf of the Elder One.</td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>Stroud (conditional): An Orlesian Grey Warden.</td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
            </tab>
        </tabs>
    </chapter>
    <chapter title="Gameplay and Combat"
             section="Show Gameplay and Combat">
        <list>
            <li>Although touted as an "open world" game at E3 2013 presentation, the developers quickly clarified that
                Inquisition is not an open world in the same way as The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim, but instead simply
                feature larger locations than Origins and Dragon Age II with more exploration freedom.[23] There are 10
                large "open world" locations in the game. Gameplay continues post story completion, as opposed to
                retroactive DLC such as in Dragon Age II.
            </li>
            <li>It is the first game in the series to feature mounts. The dialogue wheel, first featured in Dragon Age
                II, returns. Like in Dragon Age II, the wheel displays the type of emotion that matches your dialogue
                choice.
            </li>
            <li>As in both previous installments, the player character can be one of three classes: warrior, rogue, or
                mage, with three specializations for each available later in the game. The player has the ability to
                choose one of 4 playable races - human, dwarf, elf or qunari - of either male or female gender. Body
                sliders are unavailable to customize the player character's physique; rather, the engine supports
                differing body shapes for each race.[24] Two voice sets are available for each gender: in the
                English-language version of the game, one has a British accent, and the other an American one.
            </li>
            <li>Like the Warden, the Warden-Commander, and Hawke in previous titles, the Inquisitor can recruit
                companions. There are a total of 9 possible party members who can be recruited. All companions can be
                customized via armor and in-class weapon style. Similar to Dragon Age: Origins, some companions can
                leave the party if approval ratings are too low, and it is possible to only have one companion remaining
                in the end.
            </li>
            <li>Part of the gameplay of Inquisition involves obtaining and maintaining power in various regions of the
                map. In part, this is done through strongholds, which can be seized and used to accomplish various
                tasks, and which serve as a hub for promoting the interests of the Inquisition.
            </li>
            <li>While playing, the GUI for Inquisition includes a radar displaying important points and foes. The game
                can be played using a tactical camera view (where the party is controlled from overhead), or from the
                third person.
            </li>
            <li>Combat in Dragon Age: Inquisition has a greater focus on strategy than does Dragon Age II. Party health
                doesn't regenerate automatically after an encounter as it did in Dragon Age II and Dragon Age: Origins,
                and mage characters are not able to repeatedly cast, or "spam," healing spells. Similarly, the ability
                to carry healing items is limited, though the maximum number can be increased by certain perks.
            </li>
            <li>With regards to the PC edition of Inquisition, the tactical quickbar is locked at 8 slots, because,
                according to Laidlaw, "32 abilities (along with passives/upgrades) across the party provides a broad
                spectrum of tactical options."[25]
            </li>
            <li>Griffon Wing Keep, A possible Inquisition stronghold</li>
            <li>During fights, the environments may be exploited and manipulated to a greater degree than in Dragon Age
                II. This capacity goes both ways, however. For example, a mage character may cast an "ice wall" spell to
                create cover on a battlefield or hem an enemy into a corner—a similar idea to a mage casting a fire
                spell after using a grease spell in Dragon Age: Origins—but the enemy may respond by melting the ice
                wall, eliminating the player's advantage.
            </li>
        </list>
    </chapter>

    <chapter title="Gallery"
             section="Show Gallery">
        <img src="DA1.jpg" alt="DA1" width="500"/>
        <img src="DA2.jpg" alt="DA2" width="500"/>
        <img src="DA3.jpg" alt="DA3" width="500"/>
    </chapter>

</topic>
