<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "https://resources.jetbrains.com/stardust/html-entities.dtd">

<topic xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://resources.jetbrains.com/stardust/topic.v2.xsd"
       xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
       title="Dragon Age: Origins"
       id="Dragon_Age__Origins">
    <include src="ReuseMe.xml" include-id="reuse_DA_img"/>
    <chapter title="Key features" id="key-features">
        <procedure style="choices" id="features-list">
            <step>
                <p>Six unique origin stories, each with a story that affects the game as a whole:
                </p>
                <list type="decimal">
                    <li>City Elf</li>
                    <li>Dalish Elf</li>
                    <li>Dwarf Commoner</li>
                    <li>Dwarf Noble</li>
                    <li>Human Noble</li>
                    <li>
                        <anchor name="fav-story"/>
                        Magi
                    </li>
                </list>
            </step>
            <step>Three base classes to choose from: <path>.rogue</path>, <path>.warrior</path> or <path>.mage</path>.
            </step>
            <step>Three playable races: dwarf, human, and elf.</step>
            <step>Party-based gameplay with the player's character, plus up to three other characters chosen from a
                larger
                pool
                during the game.
            </step>
            <step>Combat is real-time pause-and-play tactical. This means that you select an enemy to begin attacking
                automatically, and at any point can pause the game to select commands.
            </step>
            <step>The camera provides an over-the-shoulder viewpoint when zoomed in, or an isometric-style viewpoint
                when
                zoomed out, although on the console editions, zooming, and therefore the isometric-style viewpoint, is
                unavailable.
            </step>
            <step>Spell interactions (for example a blizzard spell can put out fires, and fire spells can ignite grease
                from a grease
                spell).
            </step>
            <step>Depth-of-field effects which can be switched off via the options menu.</step>
        </procedure>
        <tip>
            <p>
                <keyword>BioWare</keyword>
                has released a regular edition of <control>Dragon Age: Origins</control> as well as special editions for
                collectors.
            </p>
        </tip>
        <warning>
            <p>
                <control>Dragon Age: Origins</control>
                is the first <keyword>BioWare</keyword> game developed for the PlayStation 3
            </p>
        </warning>
        <note>
            <p>
                The developers have cited "realistic" fantasy fiction such as <emphasis>George R. R. Martin's A Song of
                Ice and
                Fire
            </emphasis> series and fantasy paintings by artists such as Frank Frazetta as inspiration for the game.
            </p>
        </note>
    </chapter>
    <chapter title="Links" id="links">
        <p>
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml"/>
        </p>
        <p>
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml">DA starting page</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <a href="https://dragonage.fandom.com/wiki/Dragon_Age:_Origins">Link to wiki</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <menupath>Origins | Key Features | Features list</menupath>
            <a anchor="features-list">Link to Key features procedure</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <a anchor="fav-story">Link to Magi in list</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml" anchor="gameplay">Link to another page with anchor</a>
        </p>
        <p>
            <a href="NotExisting.xml" nullable="true">Link to not existing page</a>
        </p>
    </chapter>
    <chapter title="Downloadable content" id="downloadable-content">
        <deflist>
            <def title="A Tale of Orzammar">
                Tapster's Tavern is the one place where all levels of the rigidly stratified Dwarven society can meet.
                As such, it is an excellent place for deals to be made - often of a somewhat illicit nature. You've
                heard word that a Dwarven Noble is looking to hire an adventurer for a small foray into the Deep Roads.
                It should pay well - and, perhaps give you some insight into the politics of Orzammar. Knowledge that
                can be worth far more than gold...
            </def>
            <def title="Warden's Keep">
                Centuries before the events of Dragon Age: Origins, the Grey Wardens of Ferelden took up arms against
                their kingdom's rulers. This tumultuous event led to the expulsion of the Grey Wardens from Ferelden,
                leaving their ancient fortress of Soldier's Peak to the ravages of time. This downloadable content
                provides the Warden with an opportunity to aid Levi Dryden in redeeming his family name by proving that
                Sophia Dryden, his great great grandmother and commander of the Grey Wardens at Soldier's Peak, acted
                honorably.
            </def>
        </deflist>
    </chapter>

    <seealso>
        <category ref="DA1">
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml">Category 1. Link 2</a>
        </category>
        <category ref="DA2">
            <a href="Dragon_Age_2.md">Category 2. Link 1</a>
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml">Category 2. Link 2</a>
        </category>
        <category ref="DA3">
            <a href="Dragon_Age__Inquisition.md">Category 3. Link 1</a>
            <a href="Dragon Age-default.xml">Category 3. Link 2</a>
        </category>
    </seealso>
</topic>
